Come to the night, the car is laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secret sun fall
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
The rhythm, yeah, yeah, yeah, flow
Hearts in the balance, every card an open door
Feel the romance in every arcane lore
Hold on a second, I'm going to do something so we'll just play a few minutes, I'll have to play a few songs.
With nothing left, but haunted highs A thousand no's, a million tries
Still, Joni's name was in my cries Every fall became a step I had to take
They tried to dim the fire in my chest
But Joni whispered, don't you rest
Like a seashell spell
Alexander's preaching with a tan
So divine, sunscreen forgotten
He's turning to bright
With a lobster, people red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
that his whispers the pot can't wait.
Alexanderizes halo of foam, welcome microstations
to your new home.
With the lobster people, red and raw, snapping our claws
at the cosmic law.
People red and raw snapping our claws at the cosmic law
It's parade
You drew your truth in silent lines
Symbols bleeding through the veil
Lost taste in like red berries
Sweet but laced with hate
Hey, what if we just have to lose
Your gift they laughed when I fell but I danced in the dirt every scar I got just rewrote my worth all I ever wanted was to free
I just need to remodel as people come back and stuff.
Okay, I was waiting to do this presentation. If you'd like to do Spunky, if you want to do a
reading, come up on panel. And then I have another big collective horoscope, so I do it for everybody
If you have any questions about anything and ban words, well, with the words, I don't like the words people use though.
That's some of the words, right? Or I don't like the context where people have been using some words.
It's always banned them, but when I have someone like legitimate, besides Smelly, telling me about it, then maybe I'll consider it.
Oh, you want to do a private reading? I can do it. Yeah, however you want to do it. You can, if you want to do it on stream, if you want to do it private, sure.
Whatever you'd like to do I can do it like on on
Discord I
Can download anything else too if you want or I can like do it over the phone on anything. Hey, what's up?
Hello
He was covered it was always the fake ghost but no one could see him so
It's turned so cold. I know it's I know it's so cold isn't it cold? Hey Apollo Apollo's definitely mob material
I'm sorry. I modded everybody, but I had to like
See who would come back and like he was still here, and I just wanted to
Oh on straggler I was just to see I
Was one I was just to see I was like to get test. I wasn't even here. I had a I had a AI running it
I
Made the chat cold strongly well
OK, well, anyway, I'll start my thing,
but I just wait for my slideshow to be completed.
And then I'm going to be using the slideshow
with every reading.
So I can see the easily what sign I'm on is up.
And so can you guys?
OK, I'm just still working on this.
So hi, guys.
Yeah.
I'll do one card readings, Nancy, if you'd like.
Oh, and I think I do have a, I think the donor must be anonymous, anonymous donor today.
Thank you so much. I was able to like get some tobacco and a couple drinks
or Samantha has a wrench, doesn't she? Samantha, comment. I'll give it back to her.
Yeah, it's in the recruitment video hold on
Are you tired of reality not glitching enough do you crave deeper thoughts, but also snacks welcome to the cult of psyche
Still not convinced
Apply telepathically or just follow us.
There's so many cool things.
It has Carro Car readings,
it has astrology, as you can make sigils on it.
You can, there's advertising on it.
There's like the panel versus IP2 thing on it.
There's my website and everything with me,
and there's like videos playing,
there's like mysteries on the website,
there's secret Easter eggs you can find,
and there's a token system.
I mean, it's like so cool.
And then it's like, oh, well, okay, we have it ready,
but we can't deploy it.
You have no contact customer service.
and it comes to a customer service.
Oh, well, we're gonna work on that.
I mean, upcoming fix, it can be like a year
before they fix it, so I can actually deploy it.
And it's like, that's kind of annoying.
Because I made this, I put a lot of money into it too,
and it's like, I don't know what I'm gonna do with that.
So, yeah, what else?
Oh, yeah, my sorry, my camera's on the table for this stuff.
Okay, yeah, let me play the page.
Okay, yeah, I'm gonna say a little bit like, you know, it's one of those off days, but
I'm cool because thank you. I'm cool. Thank you so much. You're cool, too. You guys are cool
Okay, hold on. If you guys want anything, I always got you. Okay, hold on a second.
What do I got?
Page?
So you're here.
The fairway, sun in her hair, maple leaves falling, she don't seem to care.
She lines up a shot, swing, smooth, no range
That's my Canadian darling
That's Prairie Page
Cards on the table, incense in the air
Tarot spread open
She reads like a prayer, sweet voice humming, heart full of sage
Every word she speaks feels like a golden page
Oh prairie page, wild and free, cool as a breeze through the evergreens
Alexander's heart's gone all the way lost and that's smiling those prairie days
In bed as my prairie page
My prairie page
From the Rockies to the lakes her laughter flies
Nor the lies dancing in her eyes
She don't fit
The spark in the flames
Oh prairie page, your pure gold rain
You and your golfing wild in the rain
Terror queen with that gentle grace
You light up the coldest place
Yes, she's a w...
conspiracy dreams talking cults in the desert sands tattoo maps and shaking hands she's got
screenshots names and days a tinfoil halo ceiling faiths in a chatroom chapel saints confess every
broadcast feels like a holy mass she's cool she's hot she might be right
She say next
Crazy close games and traffickers
Crystals leave with the digital saboteurs
Truth or fiction doesn't matter much
She's fire and static and
She's part over cold, part in a net myth, half the room's scared
The rest subsist, her eyeliner is sharp as a truth dissected
And everything relieves the chat infected
You can laugh, but you're still tuned in
Because she's chaos wrapped in porcelain skin
Crystal Marie
Hey page you want to come up and talk to Johnny for a second. Johnny wants to come up. I don't know Johnny is maybe
in the stream behind the stream
She'd love to meet you. Hey guys, how are you?
I'm just having a drink and like a smoke and
sit with a Rudy
Kind of quiet day, but
Play some music for you
Sege TV cold of Sege
Garden of broken gods. We plant our screens like seeds out of pixels prayer grows
We call it a cult, but it's really a communion between the wound and the one who tends it
We are gathered in the glow of screens our rosaries made of emojis our hymns corrupted files
Yet still we rise singing through distortion the cult of psyche burns in the bandwidth
That was Lenore recorded that herself for the for the cult she wanted me to put that up as her own message
Okay
Who's this it's Apollo Apollo hey, hey, hey, hi
How are you sauce?
How are you sir? I'm I'm doing okay. I'm good. I'm very happy. I
Have a surprise for you. Oh shit
Wait, do you want to see it?
Okay, I'm scared of you. I don't know what I did
You have
You weird sometimes, you know, I don't know what's coming. Okay. Let me see. Let me see we're some only sometimes I'm weird
Sometimes yes, okay
Well, one second, I'm just gonna get it for you, huh?
Okay, ready
I think so.
It's just a press.
Okay.
What's coming?
Can you see it? Hold on.
See it?
Oh yeah!
Oh man, I love this song.
That's my girl Chrissy.
She sounds like Lady Gaga.
When you go down to a low
Thank you song to my family, okay?
On the chain me and they all love it.
Thank you, man.
Thank you.
This person, hold on one second.
I see like a person, I don't believe it's a person.
It might be somebody else, hold on.
Okay, it's a, it would be a special guest or not.
Hello?
Oh, it was a fake.
It was a fake beta.
It was a fake beta, everybody.
It was a fake beta coming up.
that's it people don't have a life with this bomb bombing shit grow up idiots
no I almost thought B was gonna come say hi for a second and then no
yeah maybe who knows no she'll never come she'll never come say hi
no it's over it's over
but it's okay you don't know you don't know I think I don't I in my opinion I
don't think she really hates you like I said before too many snakes are put
poison in her in her ears you know I know but they're like pretty snakes oh my
gosh excuse me I'm so sorry I'm sorry I wasn't very
a gay person like to do that.
That's not your real gay life.
No, it's not really gay life.
People are like, they're like just like, you know, just now.
I don't know, hey, I don't know if you saw it.
A few days ago, I was on Beta's panel, okay?
And there was this weird guy coming up.
I think he was...
No, no, no, no, no, no. Mason is normal. For me, I don't have nothing against Mason.
He is harmless. He don't want to harm them.
No, I don't know who is the name.
He was a new panel too, one time, and it's always the same.
This guy is sucking this dick. This guy is sucking this dick. This guy is gay.
About J-Doc. And now he... because I...
Don't know I don't I don't pay attention on doing this name for me. They're all these screaming idiots are the same
These sounds like black RG with you. Hey. Hey, how are you?
They
I'm okay
Damn the cats and the dog the cat and the dog
Got in a fight. Oh, no, you know, and I'm the one that gets beat up
Um
What kind of cat is it? It's like German Germany vs.
Siam or something because they're German. She's just a regular
Alley cat that I adopted
Alley way the alley she's a scrapper. Okay. She's a scrapper and so
Since bird passed away. We have a shifting in the eye the hierarchy of things here
And so now she started coming in when the doors open
And I have the gate up so the other German Shepherd can't get her well that German Shepherd jump just jumps over the gate
You know, it's no big deal. It's just a gate
Anyway, and they get into it and you know how cats are psyche, right?
They'll they prance around and they'll wiggle the end of their tail and like
Like they're trying to entice you. Yeah, yeah to fuck with them
Yeah, so it doesn't take much for a germy shepherd to fuck with you. So
And the cab versus a dog is like to forget about it. It's all it's all mind games, right?
Exactly. And so here I go trying to scoop up the cat
So the dog doesn't kill her
Oh, my gosh, and um the cat will figure it. I mean she'll just say, you know, yes
So you got a new dog Amanda. No, I've always had to I've always had to oh, I didn't know that. Okay
Yeah, yeah, Taylor's mother German shipper
She's a quiet one
She's actually older than bird was
Apollo I don't want to to to bring back how old was Betty so 2017 what we see I
adopted her no no no no hang on I adopted her in 2018 and she was two years
Oh
German means no, right? Yes, it means no
Yeah
I mean is like are you saying nine or no sometimes? I mean she hadn't worked she had only been trained
For a short time and worked for a short time and then was retired out because of her stomach issues
Yeah, she had a bad stomach
I'm sorry, but so but now you have another one still and so is the cat in the hierarchy up higher than the dog
Or is it how she thinks she is she thinks she is okay?
You know how cats are they don't give a shit is like nine nine nine no, I'm in charge
You know it's just like it's just um
Everybody's trying to figure out their place, I guess, and I love it on Beauty
Even she's she's living in USA, okay, but when I give a German comments over
Streamyard, she was listening, I think, you know
She was listening
Sometimes she would bark back at Apollo. Yes
This was funny. She was such a smart girl. There's another dog that a guy has that is
retired canine and
Her name is Delta
DELTA
Yeah, yeah, and he wants me to come look at her, but I'm just I'm not ready
Yeah
Yeah, I'm not ready. So I
Understand before my before before I had tracks, you know, I had
What why I don't know if it's the same name in English what why la
And she died also very young, only seven years old.
Hey, Apollo, do you know what a shot in Jäger is?
What does that mean?
Again, please.
Shot in Jäger?
Shot in Jäger.
Yeah.
Shadow Hunter, Shadow Hunter.
Okay, I was wondering.
Yeah, Rob Waller's are,
I have a friend who actually has a German Rottweiler that was imported from Germany
And he is big. He's a big boy like he kind of scares me and
I'm not afraid of dogs, but he scares me
I'm gonna make some new photos from
from Rex, and I'm going to show you someday.
Rex is really, really big at the moment.
He got really big, muscular, and then, wah!
Yeah, I love this dog.
We had a canny Corso at our local shelter that was an owner surrender and it was only a puppy
and he weighed almost a hundred pounds.
And so they were out walking him and they said, Hey, do you want to walk him?
I said, Oh sure, no problem.
I'll take him out to the walking area.
Oh my God.
I thought he was gonna pull me
Yeah, you need to
From the next dog. I'm thinking, you know, because my
You know that I'm planning to I'm planning to to leave Germany, right? You know that you keep saying that I'll believe it when I see it
The thing is the thing is I
Don't know where I don't I'm not I have three three locations
i can choose three locations at the moment canada australia or malaysia
um don't get away don't don't um why i mean some people would like it's just not my thing i mean
I
could live there
um
what if you were like what if you had only
what if you had crocodile dundee as your
boyfriend oh well that's like
That's out there, honey.
You like to live in a swamp, but like that or like Steve Irwin style, or do you want to like live in like a nice, condo, air conditioning, like in like Millbourne, where the gay parade is outside?
Well, yeah, that would be cool too. Like, I guess for them that lives in Queensland, I forget what area in Queensland, and they have a beautiful place. It's like a, you know, a very nice home, and, um...
They own a business there. I just served with Aussies when I was in Kuwait and
You like Aussies you like I love them to death like
Yes, they're like British people but with like a sense of humor and like yes
criminal criminal, you know credibility
A lot of them
I remember the ancestors are all, are all criminals.
Yeah, no.
All the English criminals got deported there.
Australia did like start Australia.
I mean, I like Canada too.
I could live in Canada.
They look so innocent.
You know, they're all like MK Ultra programmers in Canada.
I don't know about all that, but I could live in Canada if it wasn't so cold yeah
That's part of the programming
It is fucking cold in Canada
Well, so far all the Canadians are met on on this premise the sound they look like good people
I think they're aliens. They like try to
Nobody wants to go live there because it's like okay free health care. That's it
Most Canadians I have met are really laid-back. They're just different than Americans
And most Americans are aliens
Yeah, yeah, you saw you saw my response to you
No, no, no, no. If it was up, let me clear something up Apollo. Okay, he's not going to know what we're talking about.
If it was up to me, people like that person would not be able to breathe the same oxygen the rest of us do.
Do you understand?
They are a, they are a subset of the population in the United States, the criminal element, if you will.
Right, they are not people that I choose to hang out with
Nor would I ever be associated with
No, all of my friends are professionals. They have families and homes and you know
Do everything right? No, I don't deal with that kind of shit
Where do you know you know my opinion good this guy come on
All these gangster talk, you know, this New York gangster talk. Oh, I have weapons. I shoot you. I turn blah, blah, blah
Yeah
They're all act up like like they are some sort of John Wick
Well
No, you don't yes, I love Keanu Reeves. Okay. He is sexy. I love Keanu Reeves
But I will say this if you're in a gang and you were on YouTube
You are not bragging about the fact that you're in a game. I know that to be a fact
Who's in a game Amanda or or Paul are you in a game?
No, why do you say I think Apollo isn't a game he's like he like comment like no, I'm not shut up. No
Double-ganger in the job. Are you a doppelganger Apollo?
He's a great gangster. He's a great gangster. I'm not a gangsta. No, I'm far away from a gangster
Are you you're you're you know, like I'm being I'm against all violence after I left him over the Greek military
I made a sweet a swat him as I make how to say it I swear that I never touch a gun again
Where have a he's said he needs my gun one time in experimenting. Oh
The fuck no
Okay, never mind. Just ignore that question. Yes, you are you are in a weird mode today
I'm so sorry. Hey, um
You're an ms. 13 a big lips is that is that I think from El Salvador?
She's from one of those Mexican drug trafficking. If you have if you are truly in a gang you do not get on YouTube talking about the people you
That's what's weird for me
Remember he said on panel that he's convicted as he was in jail and then he comes on panel and blocking up a bragging
About all the crimes and weapons he collecting
How stupid are these people?
We're talking about another chatter. I don't even want to mention his name cuz he's fucking trash. You don't know him
Let's just leave it at that. I'm sorry
No
You know if you are criminal and you know about gang violence and gun violence you don't go on panel and break about it
Well, I mean if you like, you know, if you really if you have a no no life, you don't hey, oh and Jeffers
Who's yes, exactly?
Jeffers is a poor bomber. Oh
Another one. Oh
Hello hi, who's this my name is Jeff
I
Just hang it out. Where are you from? Yes, so Amanda
So many questions, but I'm from YouTube you do
Part of YouTube would you like a initiatory blowjob good and talk
Jefferson would you like an initiatory blow job just have to look at this eyes
Not for me not for me. No, no, no, I'll follow you just have to videotape it
I'll videotape it what the hell you should be a tape it Jefferson. Do you want to have sex with me?
Jeffers that I don't know about that sounds like it's Casey. Oh, it's Casey. I recognize it's a Sam board
Guys, it was Casey. Yeah. Oh
It was Casey's I heard Casey's voice in that
Apollo I guess we're my boyfriend is right now
Did anyone hear Casey? No, where?
Philadelphia Jersey out of Casey. Oh
Yeah
I had a lot of culture in the last week about something about the project
Pay the $25 fee. Because I gave you $10 last night? No, that's over. $10.25
No Jeff. That's not him. Look, he's in the chat and it's not him. And he's in the chat.
Just coincidentally, whoever it was, it was a sound board. It was KZ.
Someone is not gonna go to the triple making a KZ soundboard. I mean all they do is do like a little like um like a little like a burp clip and then like
Oh, yeah, yeah, it's KZ like that sound and then that's that's all only choosing tune sounds I need to make
There's a lot more things that go on in Philadelphia besides drugs. Oh, how about that that with a canal street?
No, I'm under
Kensington when I was there, you know, and I had a sizing tour
It was the most horrible
place I was
Seriously, I was having in
some really dirty
Well location on earth, okay, but Philadelphia was the most horrible. Okay, so is that what I said?
Hey, so this is not KZ, right? Oh, he left he left he left like a bitch like a bitch Iran
What's going on here? I have no idea
You ran
Jefferson
It's KZ. You know that lame guy KZ that no
He's like so lame they don't even remember some
She's right listen
I wasn't able to finish myself when I was on beta for a panel, okay?
I don't know the name who it was. It doesn't matter for me only because I sometimes join your panel
You know no, no, I'm gay
I'm fucking dick. I brought you back up KZ, but I knew your it was you as Jefferson people are going
Are they literally I feel like I'm running like a mental asylum for like
They're like worse than mental patients. It's like
I
Can unequivocally tell you I'm not gay. I do have a gay. I did have a gay brother
But what do you do? You did something to him man? Don't you don't hurry?
Before he died in an accident I told you that before
Oh, yeah, that's another good one.
You
With super chat pricing
Or just online
Cult
Corsaking
Yeah
Enlightenments, Merch, Size, Medium
We drink the algorithms, why?
I set up my new computer that I got for my birthday, and it's broken
Already
It would not let me get past the third screen
It asked me what country I was in it asked me what time zone I was in
Then it would go to the third one, and it would freeze up. I did that for three and a half hours. I
a thousand times. It's a brand new HP. I said fuck it. I unplugged it, put it right back in the box
and took it right back to drop it off. And so I have another one coming. It's supposed to be here,
I think either tomorrow or Friday. I got a different brand.
Well, I'm sure you you have Brian. He's an expert around this. He can't help you
Yeah, I spoke to him, you know about a lot of that and he's the one that helped me pick out the new one. Um, I
am
There is no reason that a brand new computer out of the box should be freezing up period
sometimes you have
Material or whatever, you know, it happens. It happens on YouTube. I have this computer. It was like 500 bucks
Give me a little bit more. It's a mini PC
Uh-huh, and then you just get a mini piece and that's gonna be good for like almost anything you do even like high high
High power games. The only thing is like it's not gonna connect a VR headset directly
So you have to get a different get the wireless VR set the Oculus
Something not the Rift. It's the Oculus something else, but if you want to do the VR, I mean, that's like the highest
Resolution stuff you'll need to be doing just get that separate headset that will connect to the computer anyhow
But most things will be good on a mini PC.
So get a mini PC.
I mean, I've already ordered another one.
The other one was an HP.
I've never had an HP.
And so I went back and I ordered a Dell,
because that's what I'd always had.
And every school I've ever taught in, we had Dells.
And the kids beat the hell out of those computers,
and they keep going.
So yeah, they're good computers.
I mean, it's good to have those computers.
It'll be a little bit more expensive.
I'm saying if you want like a small computer
that won't crash out, it's like a small,
a little mini PC in the future,
but you can get probably one for them.
Hi, you're kissing me?
You're always giving me kisses, guys.
I mean, I just got a middle of the line basic computer,
I don't know.
I mean, it shouldn't be crashing out already.
Maybe it's like you're, you're installing too much,
something or other, or are they-
Honey, I didn't even get past the third screen.
You don't understand.
I couldn't install anything.
That's why I'm saying it's like it's like it should be like seamless and like really easy
So if it's like that much trouble already, maybe like consider just just getting a refund for that
Oh, I've already sent it back to Amazon and told them to have their shit back. So
Oh, the north give me kisses and hugs
Casey, did you send me the 25 dollars them? They'll make you the mod
Eleanor
Lenore, do you hear it? She's calling your name.
Lenore!
She says, I want my daddy kisses.
Did you guys see Lenore did a video for me?
She did this video for me.
Where she actually talks.
Garden of broken gods will plant our screens like seeds, have a pixel, prayer grows.
We call it a cult, but it's really a communion, between the wound and the one who tends it.
We are gathered in the glow of screens, our rosaries made of emojis, our hymns, corrupted files,
yet still we rise singing through distortion. The cult of psyche burns in the bandwidth.
There we go
My outside cat is a gray and white cat and her boyfriend is all black like Lenore
Oh, he is. Oh, yes black boyfriend. That's kind of edgy. Mm-hmm. And she
She does
When I was like a she's like the Virgin Mary of the house, you know, oh listen to her purr you're purring. Yeah
Wait, you want to come out? There you go. Oh, you're praying? Yeah. Hi, sweetie. Hi
Yeah, I was just gonna I'm gonna start running a bath. I'm gonna take a bath
Um, I can't show you guys the bath, but Amanda and Paula can talk during it. They want to move back
Yeah, oh
Did you, did you still watch the Sean Ryan panel, Amanda?
I have not. I am so behind on watching his stuff. Like, between him.
Seriously, thank you for giving me. This is one of my favorite channels now.
Yeah. I saw he had a new one that came out and I really want to see it too.
And I, I watch a lot of true crime stuff and every day there's something with
a case in like a filing a motion or whatever and so I just can't get caught up
No, I don't know. I don't know. Like I said, I love
He had to what was his name? Oh
I know who you're talking about. Um, I can't think of his name either
John
Something I don't know. I forgot his name
seriously good information and good analyzing about the situation I love
when you know they listen I want oh good I have you here they say it I want to
hear by your opinion okay but because you are kind of neutral I know you don't
like Trump but your neutral brain they say it why
Why the now all the people pushing to release the app staying files, okay, which is okay. I agree
but
Why the Democrats when they are they were in charge, okay back then with John Biden
Why they didn't release it when they were in charge, you know
People have asked me that question before. Ah, I don't have the answer. I don't have the answer
I do know that the reason people are pushing so hard was Trump. It's it's something that he campaigned on
heavily campaigned on
That he was gonna release it on day one just kind of like he was gonna end the Ukraine Russian deal day one
You know grocery taxes were going down or gross food prices were going down day one. So a lot of people
I'm trying to hold his feet to the fire, so.
Okay, but the question for me, it's logical, okay?
Now the Democrats, all I see, because I was on Melit, okay?
And we watched it from hearings, you know?
And we're talking about again, about the EPSI fight,
I want to release, blah, blah, blah, okay?
But when you had the chance to release it,
why you didn't do it again I can't answer that unless they're trying to protect
someone okay unless they're trying to protect someone but knowing what I know
they're gonna have to protect a whole lot of people so there's a whole like
what I'm getting at
Is the esteemed list isn't just one side of the political aisle. It's on both. Okay. Let's not kid ourselves
Yeah, it affects heads of state, you know princes and
both political parties it doesn't
So the only thing maybe they protected somebody
Yeah, on the Sean Ryan show, you know, the he said some names, you know, like Elon Musk
King
The Prince of UK the brother or whatever
Andrew exactly and
Will Smith and then you the shit, you know, man all these people are
Perverts for all my Jesus Christ
Yeah, and the sad part about it is
It's it started long before Epstein. I mean it has been a
Thing a theme throughout history. Let's not kid ourselves. I mean, you know this
And it's it's gross and
You know even
When my great-grandfather was married, you know, he had an arranged marriage
My great-grandmother was quite a bit younger than he was
back in the day so I don't get it okay I can't just say it's an Italian thing
because it's not just an Italian thing I think that it was an acceptable
practice back in the day and you know obviously it's not now but me trying to
be as
unbiased as possible. The only thing I can say is that they're probably protecting somebody
because you're right. There were many opportunities during other, during other administrations.
Um to put that information out
um
And now no, I'm hearing that you know all these democrats are crying all
Trump is blocking the release blocking the release. Okay idiots
You had the president you can release it you set up you had to your chance
Why are you crying now shut the fuck up
Well, this is what i'm gonna say. I know a guy. He's a new york attorney and he represents one of the victims
don't even know the victim's name. I don't ask. It's none of my business. And he
has unequivocally publicly said that that list is never going to be released.
And when people ask him, he says because there's too much at stake, there's too
many people involved that it would probably bring people to their knees if
of the
the
Well, even if they release something, you don't know if it's really the truth.
Oh my God, I believe nothing, one of these politicians say nothing.
Even if they say the sky is blue, no, it's not blue, it's purple.
That's true. Like how can we even trust it? I mean the fact remains is
John F Kennedy was assassinated. We all know that we saw it with our eyes and a video, you know, what we saw and
He's no longer with us. So regardless of who did it. We can't bring him back
Doesn't change anything. Yeah, it doesn't change anything and it's unfortunate, you know, and
the Kennedy family
has been fraught with
Lots of you know tragic events over throughout history, and it's it's unfortunate
Yeah
I just fight with this casey guy. Why you don't let him up. What did you do? I don't know like so I can just said he was
Going to take a bath and left me and you up here to run the show, isn't that scary?
It's okay, I don't mind. I don't mind.
I have the worst people to talk to.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
I'm the great evil one, you know. The great evil one.
No, you are a Karen.
No, nothing, Karen.
You are Karen not gonna change if you think I'm a Karen. I can show you some real Karen's honey
You're Christine. I am not naming any names, but I'm just I do I do
You know you the the Karens at sea
You know a black man in a trench coat walking down the street in the middle of the summer and
Call the cops because oh my god. It's a black man in a trench coat. He might do something
You know, those are the Karens of the world
Yeah, trust me. You know I shared more one story when I was in
in the States and
Some stupid Karen called the cops on me because I I look like a terrorist. I
Look like a terrorist only because I have a long black bird
Back then I look like a terrorist and my my English was not
Perfect my English was not perfect, you know and I bought I bought something from their store store
And I was saying thank you, and that was enough for her to call the cops on me.
On your recent trip?
No, no, not on 2013, when I was in the state, 2013.
No, the last one was, okay, the last one was, no, I enjoyed it. I enjoyed it.
Oh, okay.
I had no problems at all, only one thing, like when they saw whoever it was called a
park ranger just for my dog, you know, but that's all, but that's all, oh yeah,
the one to the trip before Jesus Christ, this was like...
Oh Jesus, well you have to realize to everybody that isn't a pay a pasty white person in America
If you have a different accent you're automatically a terrorist like yes
September the 11th made everybody a terrorist. It wasn't an American. I'm just
Yes
Jesus they wouldn't know terrorists if it hit him in the head
Okay, so now that we have a minute to talk here, so I mentioned, I was going to mention
Syria.
I did not realize until recently when 60 Minutes did a piece on this that the now president
He used to be a member of a terrorist organization, and when I looked at his face and looked at his name, I said,
Holy shit.
Who? Who?
The president of Syria.
Oh, the puppet. He's nothing but a puppet.
Right, but, but...
When I just like for those of us that know
when I saw his face and
I saw his name. I'm like, no
No way because he was just a low tier anyway
but and
Then I looked again
I was like, no can't be and so as the lady kept asking him questions and
she said so
You know
Basically, how can you know what do you have to say for the fact that used to be a part of that organization and now you're not and
Blah-blah-blah and he tried to play it off
You know and say well, you know you live and you get older and that's not the life
You want to lead anymore basically, and I thought
Oh
Good Lord
Why do you do that? It's so rude.
That's what he's done with you. When he's born.
Why do you do this to his friends?
I didn't even know! I didn't even know!
Shut the fuck up, God, are you sick?
Oh, shit.
that is just so rude psyche. It really is. I literally didn't even mention one single name.
Anyway, so come on. Hey, no, no, no, no, like, hey, who, who got the why you, what is this
I don't I don't know. I see a name, but I don't know
No, I'll cardia ebonyu Aurora Illinois. Yeah, don't be Dawson in the fucking chat
PUSH! BDF is dead!
I ain't finished yet.
Penal verse feast, we don't starve on lies.
Your plate got nothing but recated fries.
I'm the main course.
Truth served hot.
You're the snack that everyone already forgot.
Feed us biscuits left on the shelf.
Bees on the trap, bees on the trap.
Penal life's on truth sharp like a knife.
Biscuits crumble, welcome to real life.
Bees in the trap bees in the trap
Quit doxing a chat gaudy
Oh, it's it. Oh, it's he's honey. What? Oh
Yeah, I know what you say it's his address
Dottie the Cholls
Ugh, peeper
Well, if I'm not gonna be able to talk, I'm just gonna get down. This is fucking lame.
I'll catch you later, Apollo.
Yo, have a nice day.
at the cosmic law steaming our veins salt in our eyes
and tied to gossels now we baptize
for the world and our buddha creed at the altar of hunger
psyche bleeds
page and apollo start chatting shell start to glow
go strong symbols in the undertow
god he's caused click time with faith
God's MacLaw
To people red and raw
Snapping our claws at the cosmic law
Steaming our veins saltin'
Isn't that good? Okay. Isn't that great?
Follow me.
Yes, I'm here.
Imagine your wife passes away. It's been several years and you're even older
And you can't even hardly leave the house and I come to your house one day
And I'll be like, okay. I'll wipe you
I'll um, you know, I'll be a great lover. Are you gonna turn me away from the door?
Hello
I
Told you to stop this bullshit. I told you to stop this come on
I was asking the question. So your wife has been passed away for several years. You've been lonely
Very lonely. Nobody nobody's coming to your house. Not nobody. Okay, and then I come I'm dressed like a frayer
Look at me sister. Hello, Paolo
Paolo
Hello, I think I think Apollo is some internet message and bad. I think Apollo left accidentally
But I'm sorry Paul, was that too much
Oh
Wow, oh wow, I
Can't I just want to follow it's all I just he's such a funny guy
He's so nice and funny and he's great content and then I ask him one simple question. No
He can't even say no, you know like nicely. He just leaves
Leaves me the lurch as usual
Apollo
Call me I
I did nothing wrong. I
Did nothing wrong
Permission to crash out
Ghost already did he took the whole crowd
That goes through the night
That's how you know, the haunts are live
Lights flicker, chats in the ride
And somewhere goes about to die
Heroes are loud like thunder on caffeine
Dropping stacks, cracking jokes
Keeping the scene clean
The crowd starts howling
The trolls start crying
Ghosts just grin
Remember, I was reborn
May I have permission to crash out?
Ghost already did it, took the whole crowd
Heart of gold, voice of fire
When ghost shows up, mistakes get higher
Dum dum, that's his war
Psych is proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud, proud
In a world full of clowns
He's the last of fate
When the screen went dark
He kept me awake
All the noise fades
But ghost remains
Turning pain into digital flame
May I have permission to crash out
Dumb dumb to the ones who doubt
Apollo, Apollo, are you still there?
Apollo, Apollo, Apollo, Apollo, I'm ordering McDonald's.
Give me a minute guys, I'm ordering some McDonald's.
It was just as lost
But if the dream's slow, quiet
Thank you.
I came back with the bag. I did. I dropped the bath. I'll be back with you guys. Give me a minute. Give me a minute.